John Alden Mason Papers 1904-1967 Mss.B.M384
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1926-1967; 20 linear feet
  - Grosvenor, Gilbert H (Box 18)
    - Hildebrand, J R (Box 18)
    - Mason, John Alden, Jr (Box 18)
  - Groves, G. I (Box 18)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 18)
  - Gruber, Jacob W (Box 18)
  - Guatemala, Sociedad de Geografia e Historia (Box 18)
    - Reyes M, Jose Inis (Box 18)
  - Guatemala. Instituto de Anthropologia e historia (Box 18)
  - Guatemala. Secretaria de educacion publica (Box 18)
  - Guatemalan embassy, Washington, D.C (Box 18)
  - Guggenheim, John Simon, Memorial Foundation (Box 18)
    - Butler, Mary (Box 18)
    - Davidson, D S (Box 18)
    - Fellows, Muriel H (Box 18)
    - Lara Fermandez, Carmen (Box 18)
    - Mason, Gregory (Box 18)
    - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 18)
    - Rachlin, Carol K (Box 18)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 18)
    - Taylor, Walter W (Box 18)
  - Guild, William (Box 18)
  - Gunn, Battiscombe (Box 18)
  - Gurley, Norton F (Box 18)
  - Gusicke, Albert A (Box 18)
  - Gusinde, Martin (Box 18)
  - Gustof, Stanley J (Box 18)
  - Gutentag, Yvette (Box 18)
  - Guth, Robert (Box 18)
  - Guthe, Alfred K (Box 18)
  - Guthe, Carl E (Box 18)
    - Hopkins, Hollis (Box 18)
    - Society for American Archeology (Box 18)
  - Gutierrez G, Ricardo (Box 18)
  - Haag, William G (Box 18)
  - Haas, C J (Box 18)
  - Haas, Mary R (Box 18)
  - Hackenberger, F. C (Box 18)
  - Hackett, E F (Box 18)
  - Haddon, A. C (Box 18)
  - Hadlock, Wendell S (Box 18)
  - Hafner, Kae (Box 18)
  - Hagapian, George (Box 18)
  - Hagen, Victor Wolfgang von (Box 18)
    - American Philosophical ([UNK] Von Hagen) Society (Box 18)
    - Guggenheim, John Simon, Memorial Foundation (Box 18)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 18)
  - Haldeman material (Box 18)
  - Hall, Allen (Box 18)
  - Hall, Ansel F (Box 18)
  - Hall, Eugene F., Sr (Box 18)
  - Hall, H. M (Box 18)
  - Hall, James S (Box 18)
  - Hall, John (Box 18)
  - Hallowell, Alfred Irving (Box 18)
  - Halpern, A M (Box 18)
  - Halsay, Anna C (Box 18)
  - Halseth, Odd S (Box 18)
  - Hamer, Richard (Box 18)
  - Hamill, Hugh M (Box 18)
  - Hamilton, Clayton (Box 18)
  - Hamilton, Holman (Box 18)
  - Hamilton, W. F (Box 18)
  - Hamlin, Chauncey J (Box 18)
    - Wheeler, Jane (Box 18)
  - Hammett, James W (Box 18)
  - Hammond, Harriet (Box 18)
  - Hamor, George H (Box 18)
  - Hampson, Leonard J (Box 18)
  - Handbook (Peru) (Box 18)
  - Haney, Mr (Box 18)
  - Hanke, Lewis (Box 18)
    - Litchfield, Dorothy Hale (Box 18)
    - McHugh, Jane M (Box 18)
  - Hanke, Wanda (Box 18)
  - Hanna, Paul R (Box 18)
  - Hansen, A. O (Box 18)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 18)
  - Hansen, Halvard T (Box 18)
  - Hanson, Earl (Box 18)
  - Hanson, Paul M (Box 18)
  - Harb, Victor J (Box 19)
  - Harding, Arthur L (Box 19)
  - Hargrave, Lyndon L (Box 19)
  - Haring, C. H (Box 19)
  - Haring, Clarence H (Box 19)
  - Harmer, Walter J (Box 19)
  - Harney, Mrs. Thomas P (Box 19)
  - Harney, Susan Groome (Box 19)
  - Harnish, Frances (Box 19)
  - Harnoncourt, Rene d' (Box 19)
  - Harnwell, Gaylord P (Box 19)
  - Harper, Mrs. N. Francis (Box 19)
  - Harries, Eloise Street (Box 19)
  - Harrington, J. C (Box 19)
  - Harrington, John P (Box 19)
  - Harrington, M. R (Box 19)
    - Amsden, Charles (Box 19)
  - Harris, A L (Box 19)
  - Harris, Alfred (Box 19)
  - Harris, Henry S (Box 19)
  - Harris, Marjorie (Box 19)
  - Harris, P. H (Box 19)
  - Harris, Zellig S (Box 19)
  - Harrison, J. Kearsley (Box 19)
  - Hart, A John (Box 19)
    - [Weinberg], Gladys (Box 19)
  - Hart, Brete R. (Box 19)
  - Hart, Dorothy (Box 19)
  - Hart, Walter S (Box 19)
  - Harte, Charles Rufus (Box 19)
  - Hartenstein, Paul B (Box 19)
  - Hartle, W G (Box 19)
  - Hartman, Carl G (Box 19)
  - Hartman, John P (Box 19)
  - Harvey, Theodore J., 1951; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Harvey House, Publishers (Box 19)
    - Folsom, Mary Elting (Box 19)
    - Harvey, Edith (Box 19)
    - Singer, Evelyn (Box 19)
  - Harwood, Mrs. May N (Box 19)
  - Hasselborg, Alan (Box 19)
  - Hatch, Fletcher (Box 19)
  - Hatt, Gudmund (Box 19)
  - Hatt, Robert T (Box 19)
  - Haury, Emil W (Box 19)
  - Hawkins, James (Box 19)
  - Hawkins, Mrs. C (Box 19)
  - Hay, Clarence L (Box 19)
  - Hayes, Albert O (Box 19)
  - Hayes, J Carroll (Box 19)
  - Hazelwood, J W (Box 19)
  - Healey, Giles G (Box 19)
  - Heckert, Robert A (Box 19)
  - Heflin, Eugene (Box 19)
  - Hegewisch, A E, Inc (Box 19)
  - Heine, William A (Box 19)
  - Heine-Geldern, Robert (Box 19)
  - Heitz et Cie (Box 19)
  - Held, Mrs. Margaret (Box 19)
  - Helfrich, William J (Box 19)
  - Heller, John (Box 19)
  - Hellman, Milo (Box 19)
  - Henderson, Gertrude (Box 19)
  - Hendren, Melvin W (Box 19)
  - Hendricks, Grace (Box 19)
  - Henke, Esther Mae (Box 19)
  - Henry Holt and Co (Box 19)
  - Henry, Arnold K (Box 19)
  - Henry, J. Norman (Box 19)
  - Henry, Jules (Box 19)
    - Wardle, Dr (Box 19)
  - Henry, Victor (Box 19)
  - Herbert, H. L (Box 19)
  - Herbruger Hermanos & Company (Box 19)
  - Herchelroth, B. F (Box 19)
  - Hering, W. E (Box 19)
  - Herman, Nathalie (Box 19)
    - Spinden (Box 19)
  - Hernández de Alba, Gregorio (Box 19)
  - Herr, Philip K (Box 19)
  - Herrera Tejeda, Luis (Box 19)
  - Herring, Hubert (Box 19)
  - Hershey Community House (Box 19)
    - Billow, W P (Box 19)
  - Hershey, Ezra (Box 19)
  - Herskovitz, Melville J (Box 19)
  - Herzog, George, 1939-1958 (Box 19)
  - Hesse, Curtis J (Box 19)
  - Hester, Charles A (Box 19)
  - Hettick, W L (Box 19)
  - Hetzler, Herman G (Box 19)
    - Green, Otis H (Box 19)
  - Heuson, Edith Burton (Box 19)
  - Hewes, Gordon W (Box 19)
  - Hewins, John S (Box 19)
  - Hewitt, Ida M (Box 19)
  - Heyden, Doris (Box 19)
  - Heydenburk, Frank H (Box 19)
  - Heye, George G. (Box 19)
    - Burnett, E K (Box 19)
  - Heyerdahl, Thor (Box 19)
  - Hibben, Frank C (Box 19)
  - Hickman, Lucie B (Box 19)
  - Hickox, Ann (Box 19)
  - Hiersemann, Karl W (Box 19)
  - Higgins, George L (Box 19)
  - Higgins, W. I (Box 19)
  - Hill, H. L (Box 19)
  - Hill, James (Box 19)
  - Hill, Mrs. John J (Box 19)
  - Hill, Julian W (Box 19)
  - Hill, R. G (Box 19)
  - Hill, Roland B (Box 19)
  - Hill, W. W (Box 19)
  - Hill, Mrs Walter Lee (Box 19)
  - Hilton, Ronald (Box 19)
  - Hinchman, Margaretta S (Box 19)
    - Gamio, Manuel (Box 19)
  - Hines, Mary (Box 19)
  - Hirschwaldsche, Buchhandlung (Box 19)
  - Hispanic Culture, Archives of (Box 19)
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania. Library (Box 19)
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania (Box 19)
  - Hoag, Selwyn B (Box 19)
  - Hobbing, Reimar (Box 19)
  - Hobe, Wallace F (Box 19)
  - Hobgood, John (Box 19)
  - Hodge, Frederick W (Box 19)
  - Hodge, Nancy (Box 19)
  - Hoffman, C. G (Box 19)
  - Hogan, Joseph T (Box 19)
  - Holcomb, R. C (Box 19)
  - Holden, Rev. J. H (Box 19)
  - Holden, W C (Box 19)
  - Holder, Lincoln (Box 19)
  - Holland, John D (Box 19)
  - Hollenbach, Marion (Box 19)
  - Hollmer, Joseph R (Box 19)
  - Holmberg, Allan R (Box 19)
  - Holstein, Otto (Box 19)
  - Holzinger, Charles H (Box 19)
  - Homan, J Albert (Box 20)
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts (Box 20)
    - Mott-Smith, Ann (Box 20)
  - Hood, Jennings (Box 20)
  - Hooker, A. H (Box 20)
  - Hooten, Adolfo de (Box 20)
  - Hooton, Earnest A (Box 20)
  - Hoover, J. W (Box 20)
  - Hoover, Larry (Box 20)
  - Hopkins, Mrs. A M (Box 20)
  - Hopkins, Dorothy Sibley (Box 20)
  - Hopkins, E. Hollis (Box 20)
    - Dorrance, Frances (Box 20)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 20)
  - Hopkins, J. G. E (Box 20)
  - Hopkins, Mrs. Moseley, Jr (Box 20)
  - Hopkinson, Edward, Jr (Box 20)
  - Horan, Catherine (Box 20)
  - Horn, Friedrich von (Box 20)
  - Horner, Eva M (Box 20)
  - Hornor, Marianna Merritt (Box 20)
  - Horsky, Brooke (Box 20)
  - Horter, Earl (Box 20)
  - Horter, Elizabeth L (Box 20)
  - Horton, Donald (Box 20)
  - Hostos, Adolfo de (Box 20)
  - Hough, Walter (Box 20)
  - Houseworth, Joseph E, Jr (Box 20)
  - Howard, Agnes McClain, 1949-1960; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Howard, Edgar B (Box 20)
    - Ray, Cyrus N (Box 20)
  - Howard, George D (Box 20)
  - Howard, Lynn E (Box 20)
  - Howard, Mac (Box 20)
  - Howe, Ralph S (Box 20)
  - Howser, Margaret B (Box 20)
  - Hoyle, Rafael Larce (Box 20)
  - Hoyo, Eugenio del (Box 20)
  - Hoyos, Luis G (Box 20)
  - Hrdlicka, Ales (Box 20)
  - Hubbard, Freeman H (Box 20)
  - Hubbell, Roman (Box 20)
  - Huber, F. F (Box 20)
  - Huger, Frank (Box 20)
  - Hughes, Percy (Box 20)
  - Hugo, E H (Box 20)
  - Hujer, Karel (Box 20)
  - Hull, Joseph W (Box 20)
  - Hunt, Bruce A (Box 20)
  - Hunter, Albert S (Box 20)
  - Hunter, Fenley (Box 20)
  - Hunter, W. S (Box 20)
  - Hurt, Wesley R (Box 20)
  - Hutchins, Robert Maynard (Box 20)
  - Hutchinson, Henry H (Box 20)
    - Griffin, James B (Box 20)
  - Hutchinson, Marion (Box 20)
  - Hutchinson, W. G (Box 20)
  - Huxley House Publishing Co (Box 20)
    - Hess, J C (Box 20)
  - Huxley Publishers (Box 20)
    - Martin, Luther, III (Box 20)
  - Ikawa, Fumiko (Box 20)
  - Illinois, State of. Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 20)
    - Smith, Elbert S (Box 20)
  - Imbelloni, Jose (Box 20)
  - Imprenta Universitaria (Box 20)
  - Indian problem in the two Americas (Box 20)
  - Indians of Pennsylvania (Box 20)
  - Ingalls, Albert G (Box 20)
  - Ingersoll, R Sturgis (Box 20)
  - Institute of Andean Research (Box 20)
  - Instituto de Antropologia E Historia (Box 20)
    - Molina, Adolfo (Box 20)
  - Instituto de Investigaciones Esteticas (Box 20)
  - Instituto Indigenistre Interamericano (Box 20)
  - Inter-American Indian Institute (Box 20)
  - International Auxiliary Language Association (Box 20)
    - Buning, de Cock (Box 20)
  - International Business Machines Corp (Box 20)
    - Hackett, E F (Box 20)
  - International Congress of Americanists (Box 20)
    - Boas, Franz (Box 20)
    - Casagrande, Joseph (Box 20)
    - Finch, Gertrude (Box 20)
    - Goddard, P E (Box 20)
    - Stevenson, Violet (Box 20)
    - Wissler, Clark (Box 20)
  - International Congress, editing job, 1957 (Box 20)
  - International Exchange Service (Box 20)
  - International Journal of American Linguistics (Box 20)
    - Boas, Franz (Box 20)
    - Thompson, Stith (Box 20)
  - International Press Photo Service (Box 20)
  - International Students House (Box 20)
    - Thompson, Elmer T (Box 20)
  - International Travel Service (Box 20)
  - Intramural affairs, 1953 (Box 21)
  - Inzillo, Antonio (Box 21)
  - Inzillo, Dominio (Box 21)
  - Irwin, Cynthia (Box 21)
  - Irwin, Mrs. Ellen D (James) (Box 21)
  - Isaac Delago Museum of Art (Box 21)
  - Jackson, A. T (Box 21)
  - Jackson, Ralph W (Box 21)
  - Jacobi, A (Box 21)
  - Jacobs, Melville (Box 21)
    - Duggan, Fred S (Box 21)
    - Wardle, Hariet Newell (Box 21)
  - Jacobson, Saul (Box 21)
  - Jakeman, M Wells (Box 21)
  - James, Arthur (Box 21)
    - Mook, Maurice (Box 21)
  - James, Nancy E (Box 21)
  - Jamieson, Bernice E (Box 21)
  - Janecek, John J (Box 21)
  - Jayne, Horace H. F (Box 21)
    - Knoblock, B (Box 21)
    - Mason, John Alden, Jr (Box 21)
    - McHugh, Jane M (Box 21)
  - Jenkins, H. E (Box 21)
  - Jenks, A. E (Box 21)
  - Jenks, John Story (Box 21)
  - Jenness, Diamond (Box 21)
    - Malcolm, Wyatt (Box 21)
  - Jennings, Nora M (Box 21)
  - Jensen, Dorothy Cross (Box 21)
  - Jentes, A R &Co., Inc (Box 21)
  - Jerome, Albert, Jr (Box 21)
  - Jijón y Caamaño, J (Box 21)
  - Jijon y Caamano, Jacinto (Box 21)
  - Jiminez Moreno, Wigberto (Box 21)
  - Jochelson, Waldemar (Box 21)
  - Johansen, Ulla (Box 21)
    - Bierhenke, Wilhelm (Box 21)
    - Haberland, Wolfgang (Box 21)
    - Zimmermann, Günter (Box 21)
  - Johnson, E. R. Fenimore (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Eldridge R (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Florence M. (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Frederick, 1938-1954 (Box 21)
    Re., in part, Talamanca of Panama
  - Johnson, Frederick, reading lists (Box 21)
    - Vaillant, George C (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Irmgard W (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Jacob Bridgens, 1942-1943 (Box 21)
    Re: Campa of Peru.
  - Johnson, Jean B (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Jotham (Box 21)
    - McKern, W. C (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Lawrence (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Ruben (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Thomas R (Box 21)
  - Jolls, Mrs. C. H (Box 21)
  - Jones, Mrs. Lois B (Box 21)
  - Jones, R. L (Box 21)
  - Jones, Robert C & Ingeborg H Jones (Box 21)
  - Jones, Robert L (Box 21)
  - Jones, Stephen S., Jr (Box 21)
  - Jones, T. H (Box 21)
  - Jones, Thomas R (Box 21)
  - Jones, Volney H (Box 21)
  - Josephson, Bertha E (Box 21)
  - Joyce, Mrs. Charles D (Box 21)
  - Joyce, T A (Box 21)
  - Juan el Oso (Box 21)
  - Judd, Charles H (Box 21)
    - Diehl, Mary (Box 21)
  - Judd, Neil M (Box 21)
  - Judson Court (Box 21)
  - Junghanns, Robert L (Box 21)
  - Köbertiz, Helge (Box 21)
  - Kaempffert,Waldemar (Box 21)
  - Kahn, Carol (Box 21)
  - Kaledin, C (Box 21)
    - Augustin, J J (Box 21)
  - Kamen-Kaye, Dorothy (Box 21)
    - Gregg, Clifford C (Box 21)
  - Kaplan, Philip (Box 21)
  - Kaplan, Susan P (Box 21)
  - Kappes, Irwin J (Box 21)
  - Karger, Fritz (Box 21)
  - Karlen, Arno (Box 21)
    - Holiday (Box 21)
  - Kashevaroff, A. P (Box 21)
  - Katz, Siegfried E (Box 21)
  - Kaudern, Walter (Box 21)
    - Elander, Douglas (Box 21)
    - Keppel, Frederick (Box 21)
    - Spier, Leslie (Box 21)
  - Kauffmann Doig, Federico (Box 21)
  - Kausler, Regis A (Box 21)
  - Keeler, Clyde (Box 21)
  - Keightley, David N (Box 21)
  - Keleman, Pál (Box 21)
  - Kelley, J Charles (Box 21)
    - Fejos, Paul (Box 21)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 21)
  - Kelly, A. R (Box 21)
    - Wardle, Hariet Newell (Box 21)
  - Kelly, Catharine (Box 21)
  - Kelly, David H., 1957; 7 items (Box 21)
    Re: comparison of Polynesian and Uto-Aztecan languages (Kelly's dissertation).
  - Kelly, Isabel (Box 21)
    - Chilcote, C G (Box 21)
    - Gifford, E W (Box 21)
  - Kelly, Leon (Box 21)
  - Kelly, Matthew (Box 21)
  - Kelsey, Vera (Box 21)
  - Kempton, J H (Box 22)
  - Kendall, Alice W (Box 22)
    - Newark Museum (Box 22)
  - Kendall, Leslie (Box 22)
  - Kendrick, B. E (Box 22)
  - Kenndrick, Alexander (Box 22)
  - Kent, Donald (Box 22)
  - Kent, Mrs. H (Box 22)
  - Kent, Roland G (Box 22)
  - Kenton,Edna (Box 22)
  - Kentucky, University of (Box 22)
    - Webb, William S (Box 22)
  - Keppel, F B (Box 22)
    - Russell, J (Box 22)
  - Kernan, Henry S (Box 22)
  - Keystone Automobile Club (Box 22)
  - Kidd, Gordon (Box 22)
  - Kidd, Kenneth E (Box 22)
  - Kidder, Alfred V (Box 22)
    - Gamiz, Everardo (Box 22)
    - Pattee, Richard (Box 22)
    - Ritchie, Eleanor W (Box 22)
  - Kidder, Alfred, II (Box 22)
  - Kielbowitz, Stephen (Box 22)
  - Kier, Charles F., Jr (Box 22)
  - Kier, Charles F (Box 22)
  - Kight, Morris L (Box 22)
  - Kilburn, Paul (Box 22)
  - Kimble, Fisk (Box 22)
  - Kimbrough, Mr. & Mrs (Box 22)
  - Kimmel, William G (Box 22)
    - Babcock, Faith (Box 22)
  - King, Arthur C (Box 22)
  - King, Clyde L (Box 22)
  - Kingsbury, Isaac W (Box 22)
  - Kirchhoff, Paul (Box 22)
    - Christensen, Bodil (Box 22)
  - Kirkpatrick, John B (Box 22)
  - Klein, Alfred M (Box 22)
  - Klein, Lillian A (Box 22)
  - Kleinmann, Mrs. Lynn (Box 22)
  - Kline, H. F (Box 22)
  - Klodic, R (Box 22)
  - Kluckhohn, Clyde (Box 22)
  - Knapp, Martha (Box 22)
  - Knight, Mabel F (Box 22)
    - Fewkes (Box 22)
  - Knight (Box 22)
  - Knoblock, Mrs. Richard N (Box 22)
  - Knowles, Nathaniel (Box 22)
  - Knox, Lucy Perry (Box 22)
  - Knutsford, The Viscount (Box 22)
  - Koch, Robert F (Box 22)
  - Kochtitzky, R B (Box 22)
  - Koehn, Constance (Box 22)
  - Koffman, Nathan (Box 22)
  - Kohak, Barbara (Box 22)
  - Kohler, C. C (Box 22)
  - Kohman, Truman P (Box 22)
  - Korn, Louis J (Box 22)
  - Kosinski, Edward (Box 22)
  - Koza, Robert W (Box 22)
  - Kramer, Gerhardt (Box 22)
    - Middle American Research Institute (Box 22)
  - Kratz, Thomas F (Box 22)
  - Krause, Fritz (Box 22)
  - Krauskopf, Manfred (Box 22)
  - Krauss, Babette (Box 22)
  - Kretschmar, Arthur W (Box 22)
  - Krickenberg, Walter (Box 22)
  - Krieger, Alex D & Margie Kriege (Box 22)
  - Krieger, Alexander (Box 22)
  - Kroeber, Alfred L., 1927-1945; 3 folders (Box 22)
    Includes comments on Mason's Papago grammar, publication, Juan Dolores.
    - Boas, Franz (Box 22)
    - Lilge (?), Evelyn (Box 22)
    - Lowie, Robert H (Box 22)
    - Sauer, Carl (Box 22)
    - Thompson, Raymond H (Box 22)
    - Whipple, Mary Anne (Box 22)
  - Kroeber, Mrs. A. L (Box 22)
  - Kruck, A (Box 22)
  - Krueger, Anna Barbara (Box 22)
  - Kruse, P. Albert (Box 22)
  - Kubler,George (Box 22)
  - Kurath, Gertrude (Box 22)
  - Kurath, William (Box 22)
  - Kutsche, Paul (Box 22)
    - Agogino, George (Box 22)
  - La Farge, Oliver (Box 22)
  - Labastille, Irma Goebel (Box 22)
  - LaBrun, Thomas J (Box 22)
  - Lacey, Frederick W (Box 22)
  - Ladd, Robert (Box 22)
  - LaFarge, Consuelo (Box 22)
  - LaFarge, Oliver (Box 22)
  - Laing, Thelia Conrad (Box 22)
    - Castro, Antonio P (Box 22)
  - Landis, E. M (Box 22)
  - Landis, Paul H (Box 22)
  - Lane, Allen (Box 22)
  - Lane, Jean McIver (Box 22)
  - Lane, Miss (Box 22)
  - Langdon, Clara D (Box 22)
    - McHugh, Jane M (Box 22)
  - Lange, Francisco Curt (Box 22)
  - Langenkamp, Arthur, L (Box 22)
  - Langford, George (Box 22)
  - Langman, Ida K (Box 22)
  - Lanke, H. C (Box 22)
  - Lanks, Herbert C (Box 22)
  - Lanning, Catherine (Box 22)
  - Lara Fernandez, Carmen (Box 23)
  - Lara, F. Rodrigo de (Box 23)
  - Larco Herrera, Rafael (Box 23)
  - Larco Hoyle, Rafael (Box 23)
  - Larkin, Roosevelt and Larkin (Box 23)
    - Larkin, Thomas, III (Box 23)
  - Larrabee, Marshall H (Box 23)
  - Larsen, Helge (Box 23)
  - Laufer, Berthold (Box 23)
  - Lauriault, Erwin H (Box 23)
  - Law, Mrs. J (Box 23)
  - Lawrence, Clifford O (Box 23)
  - Lawrence, W. C (Box 23)
  - Laws, Elizabeth (Box 23)
    - Rodriguez, Mario Michael (Box 23)
  - Lawson, Larry (Box 23)
  - Leaning, Mary C (Box 23)
  - Leap, Fred C (Box 23)
  - Ledger Syndicate (Box 23)
    - Watkins, John Elfreth (Box 23)
  - Ledig, Elizabeth L (Box 23)
  - Ledoux, Pierre (Box 23)
    - Ledoux, Louis V (Box 23)
  - Lee, George O (Box 23)
  - Leechman, Douglas (Box 23)
  - Leeds, Arthur N (Box 23)
  - Lefevre, Edwin (Box 23)
  - Legram, L (Box 23)
  - Lehmann, Henri (Box 23)
  - Lehmann, Walter (Box 23)
  - Leichliter, Edward (Box 23)
  - Lekis, Lisa (Box 23)
  - Lemaire, M L J (Box 23)
  - Lemal, D. J (Box 23)
  - Lenape Club (Box 23)
    - Parmenter, G. L (Box 23)
  - Lenders, E W (Box 23)
  - Lendon, Castillo (Box 23)
  - Leon Marques, Adrian F (Box 23)
  - Leon, Frances (Box 23)
  - Leonard, Juan (Box 23)
  - Leslie, Vernon (Box 23)
  - Lesser, Alexander (Box 23)
  - Leverenz, Vergene F (Box 23)
  - Levi, Mario Attilio (Box 23)
  - Levin, Leon Lewis (Box 23)
  - Levin, Octavio Garcia (Box 23)
  - Levinthal, Sonia (Box 23)
    - Lothrop, Eleanor (Box 23)
  - Levi-Strauss, Claude, 1942; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Levy, Howard S (Box 23)
  - Lewes Special School District (Box 23)
    - Omwake, H Geiger (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Mary Butler (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Mary (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Mr. and Mrs. A. B (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Mrs. Harmon (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Shippen (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Walter P (Box 23)
  - Lhuillier, Alberto Ruz - see Ruz (Box 23)
  - Libby, W E (Box 23)
  - Libby, W F (Box 23)
  - Libraria Sigla XX (Box 23)
  - Library of Congress (Box 23)
    - Blickensderfer, Joseph P (Box 23)
    - Wiggins, Edna (Box 23)
  - Lichwa, Edward (Box 23)
  - Lid, Nils (Box 23)
  - Liendo Lazarte, Manuel (Box 23)
  - Light, Raymond U (Box 23)
  - Light, Richard (Box 23)
  - Lilien, Rose (Box 23)
  - Lillie, Frank R (Box 23)
  - Lilly, Eli (Box 23)
  - Lima, Peru. Museo Nacional (Box 23)
    - Hurtado, F S (Box 23)
  - Lincoln, Anna T (Box 23)
  - Lindblom, K Gerhard (Box 23)
  - Linden Museum. Stuttgart, Germany (Box 23)
  - Lindgren, Ethel John (Box 23)
  - Lindsay, Alexander J (Box 23)
  - Lines, Jorge A (Box 23)
  - Lingelbach, William Ezra (Box 23)
  - Linguistic Society of America (Box 23)
    - Cowan, J M (Box 23)
  - Linguistics: (Box 23)
    - International phonetic alphabet symbols (Box 23)
    - Kagaba texts (Box 23)
    - Maratin (Box 23)
    - Winton (Box 23)
    - Patwin (Box 23)
      General note
      Notes taken from [s.] Powers
    - Andulucian phonetic characteristics (Box 23)
    - Linguistic groups north of Mexico (Box 23)
    - Maratin song (Box 23)
    - Spanish-Maya-Mame-Huaxtec words (Box 23)
    - Suisun vocabulary (Box 23)
    - Pepecano notes (Box 23)
    - Yana-Salinan lexical correspondence (Box 23)
  - Linné, Siguald (Box 23)
  - Linton, Ralph (Box 23)
    - Fejos, Paul (Box 23)
  - Lippincott, J B Co (Box 23)
    - Mehl, Alberta (Box 23)
  - Lippincott, J. Penrose (Box 23)
  - Lippincott, Virginia (Box 23)
  - Lippincott, Mrs. William (Box 23)
  - Lira, Jorge A (Box 23)
  - List, George (Box 23)
  - Lister, Robert E (Box 23)
  - Liverpool Museum (Box 23)
  - Livingston, Russell A (Box 23)
  - Llausás, Antonio López (Box 23)
  - Lloyd, Malcolm, Jr (Box 23)
  - Locke, L. Leland (Box 23)
  - Lockhard, D. W (Box 23)
  - Lodholz, Mrs. Edward (Box 23)
  - Logan, E B (Box 23)
  - Loma, Francisco C (Box 23)
  - Lomax, Alan (Box 23)
  - Long, Boaz (Box 23)
  - Long, Breckinridge (Box 23)
  - Long, Richard C. E (Box 23)
  - Longacre, Robert E (Box 23)
  - Lonsinger, Nora M (Box 23)
  - Lopez (Box 23)
  - Lopez, Amy M (Box 23)
  - Losey, Charles (Box 23)
  - Lothrop, Samuel K & Eleanor (Box 23)
  - Lothrop, Samuel K (Box 23)
  - Louisiana State Exhibit Building (Box 23)
  - Lovén, Sven (Box 23)
  - Lowe, Harold T (Box 23)
  - Lowe, Harry (Box 23)
  - Lowie, Robert H (Box 23)
    - Beals, Ralph L (Box 23)
    - Block, Gwen (Box 23)
    - Kroeber, Alfred L (Box 23)
  - Lucas, John D., Printing Company (Box 23)
  - Lucena,F Seco de (Box 23)
  - Lucy, Charles L (Box 23)
  - Ludendorff, H (Box 23)
  - Ludy, Hotel (Box 23)
  - Luiken, H A (Box 23)
  - Luma, Carlos (Box 23)
  - Lumsdrn, Edith R (Box 23)
  - Luna, Carlos L (Box 23)
  - Lunardi, Federico (Box 23)
  - Lundell, C L (Box 23)
  - Luther, Frederic P (Box 23)
  - Lybrand, Ross Bros., and Montgomery (Box 23)
  - Lykins, Robert W (Box 23)
  - Lyle, Mrs. George (Box 23)
  - McAdams, Mrs. Leslie (Box 24)
  - McAllister, John (Box 24)
  - McBryde, F Webster (Box 24)
  - McCann, Thomas J (Box 24)
  - McCarthy, Joseph E (Box 24)
  - McCary, Ben C (Box 24)
  - McClelland, George William (Box 24)
  - McClurg, A C & Co (Box 24)
  - McComas, H C (Box 24)
    - McComas, Edith R (Box 24)
  - McConnell, M Y (Box 24)
  - McCormack, Helen G (Box 24)
  - McCormick, Earl L (Box 24)
  - McCormick, Martin (Box 24)
  - McCurdy, Films (Box 24)
  - MacCurdy, George Grant (Box 24)
  - McCutcheon, Roger P (Box 24)
  - McDaniel, Walter Brooks (Box 24)
  - McDermott, John Francis (Box 24)
  - MacDonald, Arthur (Box 24)
  - MacDonald, Godfred (Box 24)
  - MacDougald, Duncan, Jr (Box 24)
  - McDougall, Elsie (Box 24)
  - McDougall, W. D (Box 24)
  - McElroy, Robert T (Box 24)
  - McFadden-MacQueen, Arthur W (Box 24)
  - MacFarlan, Donald (Box 24)
  - MacFarland, Joseph (Box 24)
  - McGovern, William M (Box 24)
  - McGowan, J. W (Box 24)
  - MacGowan, Kenneth (Box 24)
    - Beals, Ralph (Box 24)
    - Johnson, Fenimore (Box 24)
  - McGregor, John C (Box 24)
  - McHugh, Jane (Box 24)
  - McInnes, Martha H (Box 24)
  - Macintyre, Anna M (Box 24)
  - McKay, David, Co (Box 24)
    - McKay, Margery (Box 24)
  - McKern, W C (Box 24)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 24)
  - MacKaye, W V (Box 24)
  - MacKinley, W E W (Box 24)
  - McKinney, R J (Box 24)
  - MacLean, Harry I (Box 24)
  - MacLeash, Kenneth (Box 24)
  - McMann, Horace (Box 24)
  - McManus, Charles J (Box 24)
  - MacManus, Weir B (Box 24)
  - McMillion, Dimple L (Box 24)
  - MacNab, Marion L (Box 24)
  - MacNeal, Herbert P (Box 24)
  - MacNeish, Richard S (Box 24)
  - MacPhail, Dr (Box 24)
  - McQuown, Norman A (Box 24)
  - McRoberts, Reed A (Box 24)
  - Madeira, Margaret C (Box 24)
  - Maderra, Percy C., Jr (Box 24)